Federal Art Project, Photographic Division
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artist Files, circa 1920-1965, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-24; 9.6 linear feet)
  - Reinhart, Stewart, 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Reisman, Philip, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 5)
    includes photos of Reisman
  - Reiss, Lionel S., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Reiter, Freda L., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Resnick, Milton, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Rexroth, Andre, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Reznikoff, Misha, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Ribak, Louis, 1937-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Rice, Dustin, 1939, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Richter, Mischa, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Richter, Nathan, 1937-1940, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Riciardi, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Rico, Dan, 1937-1939, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Rile, Hannah S., 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Rites, Marion, 1937-1939, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 18)
  - River, Lowen E., 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Riza, Janet, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Robbins, H. D., 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Roberts, Malcolm, circa 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 22)
    includes photo of Roberts
  - Robus, Hugo, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Rodvogin, Harris, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Rogers, J., 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Rogers, Reginald Hubert, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Rohland, Paul, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Rohowsky, Meyers, 1939-1940, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Rohr, Julius, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Rollo, Joe, 1937-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Rolshoven, Julius, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 31)
    includes photo of Rolshoven
  - Romaine, Dorothy, 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Romano, Emanuel, 1936-1937, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 33)
    includes photo of Romano, 1936
  - Ronay, Stephen, 1937-1938, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Ropman, B, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Rosalie, J., circa 1936, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Rose, Iver, 1940, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Rosen, Paula, 1937-1938, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Rosene, Helene, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Ross, Fred, 1937-1940, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Ross, Louis, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 41)
    includes photos of Ross
  - Rothkowitz, Marcus, circa 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Rubitschung, Francois H., circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Ruggles, Philo B., circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Rugolo, Joseph, 1940-1942, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Rush, Olive, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Russin, Herbert, circa 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Russin, Robert, circa 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Rutledge, J., 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Saar, Richard W., 1945, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Sachs, Hugo, 1939, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Safferson, Matthew, 1940-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Saint Claire, E., 1940, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Saint Cyr, 1936, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Saint-Lanne, Louis, circa 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Saltzman, Helen, circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Sambugnac, Alexander, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Samuels, I. K., 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Sanchez, Juan, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 14)
    includes photo of Sanchez
  - Sanders, Adam A., 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Sanger, I. J., 1937-1938, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Sanger, William, circa 1939, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Santoriello, Angelo, 1940, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Saphier, C., 1939-1942, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Sarka, Charles, 1938-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Sarkadi, Leo, 1937-1940, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Sasanoff, M., 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Savage, Augusta, circa 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 23)
    photo of Savage
  - Saviano, Thomas, 1939-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Sawyer, Archibald D., circa 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 25)
    photo of Sawyer
  - Scaravaglione, Concetta, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Schafer, Marjorie, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Schanker, Louis, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 28)
    includes photos of Schanker
  - Schardt, Bernard, 1938-1939, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Scheinberg, Clara, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Schewe, Theodore, 1937-1939, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Schiff, Luba, circa 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Schlazer, Michael, 1937-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Schleeter, Howard, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Schlemowitz, Abram, 1937-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Schmitz, Carl, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Schnitman, Sacha S., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Schoonmaker, Eugene Spalding, 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Schreiber, Georges, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Schulemowitz, Leo, 1940-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Schwardt, Marion, 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Schwartz, Lester O., 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Schwartz, William, circa 1938-circa 1940, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Scott, Marion, 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Seabrooke, Georgette, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 45)
    includes photo of Seabrooke, 1939
  - Segura, George, circa 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Sehlmeyer, Catharine, 1937-1940, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 47)
  - Selinkoff, Alice, 1939, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 48)
    photo of Selinkoff
  - Sembler, Arthur, 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 49)
  - Sever, Alfred, circa 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 20 (hol), Folder 50)
  - Shackelford, Shelby, 1940, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Sharp, John, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Shaw, Lillian, 1939, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 3)
    photo of Shaw
  - Sheppard, William L., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Sherman, Effim H., circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Shields, Francis Bernard, circa 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Shokler, Harry, 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Shomberg, Bertram, 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Shonnard, Eugenie, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 9)
    includes photos of Shonnard
  - Shore, 1940, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Shore, Arlene, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Shore, Lillian, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Shulgold, William, 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Shulkin, Anatol, 1936-1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Shulman, Morris, 1938-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Shuster, Will, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 16)
    includes photo of Shuster
  - Sievan, Maurice, 1940, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Silver, Helen, 1940-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Simmonds, William G., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Skolfield, Raymond, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Skoorka, Paul, 1940-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Slifkin, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Smith, David, circa 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Smith, E. F., 1939, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Smith, Jacob Getlar, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Sofo, Arthur, 1938-1940, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Sokole, Miron, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Soles, William, 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Solman, Joseph, 1937-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Soyer, Isaac, 1936-1937, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Soyer, Moses, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 31)
    includes photo of Soyer, circa 1938
  - Soyer, Raphael, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Spagna, Vincent, 1940-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Speakman, Russel, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 34)
    includes photo of Speakman, circa 1936
  - Spector, George, 1937-1940, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Spivak, Max, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Spohn, Clay Edgar, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Sprinchorn, Carl, 1936, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Springweiler, Erwin, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Stamper, Mabelle Richardson, 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Starr, Maxwell B., circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 21 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Stea, Cesare, circa 1936-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 1)
    includes photo of Stea, 1939
  - Stearn, Frank, 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Stefano, Berthe, 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Steffen, Bernard Joseph, 1938-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Stein, Hirsh, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Steinback, William, 1940, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Steinberg, Abraham, 1937-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Steinberg, E., 1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Steinlauf, Saul, 1940-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Stelback, Anna, 1937-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Stella, Joseph, circa 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Stenbery, Algot, 1938-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Steinfeld, Lawrence, 1937-1939, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Stern, Louis, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Sternberg, Harry, circa 1936, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Stewart, Dorothy N., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 16)
    photo of Stewart
  - Stone, Louis K., 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Stone, Stanford Byron, 1939-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Stott, Joseph, circa 1938, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Strack, Marjorie G., circa 1937, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Straeter, Angela, 1938-1939, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Stuart, Edie, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Suba, Niklos, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Sulmonetti, Salverio, 1938-1941, (R: 1172) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Sussman, Richard, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1172-1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Suzuki, Sakari, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 26)
    includes photo of Suzuki, 1936
  - Swanson, Bennet A., 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Swerdloff, Sam, 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Swinden, Albert, circa 1936-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Swisher, Allan, 1937-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Szanton, Beatrice, 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Tait, Agnes, circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Takis, Nicholas, circa 1940-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Tamayo, Rufino, circa 1936, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Tamotzu, Chuzo, circa 1940-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Tanzer, Julius, 1937-1940, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Taskey, Harry L., circa 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Taylor, Douglas, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Taylor, Jack, 1936, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Terrel, Elizabeth, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Thal, V., 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Theobald, Samuel, 1939-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Thieme, Anthony, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Thomas, Norman Millet, 1945, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Thorp, George, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Thrash, Dox, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 22 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Tobias, Abraham, circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Todaro, 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Todd, Bianca, 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Tofel, Jennings, circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Tolegian, Manuel, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Trentham, Eugene, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Trevasani, N., 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Tromka, Abram, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Trubach, Ernest S., 1937-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Tschacbasov, Nahum, 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Turner, Raymond, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 11)
    includes photo of Turner, 1940
  - Turner, Rene, 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Turnbull, James B., 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Tworkov, Jack, 1937-1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Ubogy, Wolf, 1938-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Ufer, Mary, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Ufer, Walter, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Ulreich, Edward, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Upjohn, Regan, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Usui, Bumpei, circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Vagis, Polygnotos George, circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Valenta, Yaroslav Henry, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Van Aaltan, Jacques, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 23)
    includes photos of Van Aaltan, 1938-1939
  - Van Raalte, David, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Van Soelen, Theodore, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Van Wolf, Henry, circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Varian, Dorothy, 1937-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Velonis, Anthony, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Vidar, Frede, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Vogel, Joseph, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Von Minckwitz, Katharine, 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Von Wicht, John, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Vrachopoulos, Demetrios, 1937-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Vuchinich, Vuk, 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Vukovic, Marko, 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Wahl, Albert, 1938-1939, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Wahl, Theodore, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Walkowitz, Abraham, 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Walsh, Barnard, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Walter, Joseph, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Warren, Wilbert, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Warsager, Hyman, 1937-1939, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Warthoe, Christian, circa 1937-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Watrous, James, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Webb, Albert J., circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Weidhaas, Ted, 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Wein, Albert, 1938-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 47)
  - Wein, Elsie, 1937-1938, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 48)
  - Weinstock, Carol, 1938-1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 49)
  - Weinstock, Saul, 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 50)
  - Weiss, Hugo, 1937-1939, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 51)
  - Weiss, Julius, circa 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 52)
  - Weiss, Reginald, 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 53)
  - Weissbuch, Oscar, 1936-1939, (R: 1173) (Box 23 (hol), Folder 54)
  - Weller, Paul, 1938-1939, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Weschler, Anita, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Wessels, Glenn, 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 3)
  - West, Pennerton, 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Wheeler, 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Wheelock, Warren, circa 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 6)
  - White, Ruth, circa 1936-circa 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Widlicka, Leopold, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Wiencek, Alicia, 1940, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Wieseltheir, Vally, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Wilenchick, Clement, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Wilks, Louis, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Williams, Frederick, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Williams, J. Scott, circa 1920, circa 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 14)
    photos of Williams
  - Williams, Mildred E., 1936, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Willis, Katharine, 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Willmott, Cyril, 1937-1939, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Wilson, John, 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Wilson, Reginald, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Wilson, Sol, 1938-1940, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Wiltz, A., circa 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Wingate, Arline, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Winograd, Ihann, 1937, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Winter, Andrew, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Wolff, Adolf, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Wolfson, A., 1941, (R: 1173) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Woodrum, V., 1941, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Wooly, A., 1939, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Wright, Mable, 1939, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Xceron, John, circa 1938-circa 1942, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 30)
    includes photos of Xceron, 1942
  - Xeneles, Phonnie, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Ximinez, A., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Yaghjian, Edmund K., 1940, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Yates, Ruth, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Yorio, Pasquale, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Yun, Tee, 1938, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Yurchemo, Basel, 1939, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Zaiden, Arthur, 1938, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Zeitlin, Alexander, 1938-1939, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Zemachson, Paul, 1937, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Zeigler, Lee Woodward, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Zilzer, Gyula, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Zimmerman, Herman, 1938-1940, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Zion, Ben, 1940, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Zingale, Santos, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Ziroli, Nicola Victor, 1940, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Zorach, William, 1940, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 47)
    includes photos of Zorach, Reginald Marsh and Louis Bouché; see also Subject Files, Art Week (Box 24, F16)
  - Zucker, 1941, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 48)
  - Zucker, Jacques, 1941, (R: 1174) (Box 24 (hol), Folder 49)
- Subject Files, 1935-1942, Series 2:; (Boxes 25-31; 2.8 linear feet)
  Photographs in this series document many of the FAP's educational activities such as classes for children and adults, primarily in New York City, and active community and federal art centers in other states including Iowa, Florida, and Washington State. Also found here are photos of non-federal public buildings decorated with FAP artwork, such as airports; photos of artists at work and demonstrating various processes; photos of exhibitions including some at the Harlem Art Center; photos documenting FAP branches including the Easel Division, the Graphic Arts Division, and the Poster Division, and other projects such as the Federal Music, Theater and Writer Projects. There is one folder of photographs of Civilian Conservation Corps camps training school. Also found here are photographs of people and events including FAP director Holger Cahill.
  One folder contains images that appear to have been taken by Berenice Abbott for the exhibition Changing New York, for the Museum of the City of New York in collaboration with the WPA.
  In addition to copy prints and scattered negatives the series also contains a transcript of a Signal Corps Photographic Center dedication.
  Photographs are arranged alphabetically by folder title/subject.
  - Airport Murals and Construction, (R 1179: 69-91) (Box 25 (hol))
    - LaGuardia Airport, circa 1938-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 1)
    - Newark Airport, circa 1940 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 2)
    - North Beach Airport, circa 1938-circa 1939 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Armed Forces, circa 1939-1945 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Art Centers, Community, (R 1178: 8-148) (Box 25 (hol))
    - Iowa, Mason City, circa 1938-circa 1939 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 5)
    - Iowa, Sioux City, circa 1937-circa 1939 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Art Centers, Federal (Box 25 (hol))
    - Arizona (Phoenix), circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 7)
    - Florida (Jacksonville, Miami, St. Petersburg), circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 8)
    - Montana (Butte), circa 1938 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 9)
    - New Mexico, circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 10)
    - North Carolina (Asheville, Greensboro, Raleigh?, Winston Salem), circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 11)
    - Ohio (Cleveland), circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 12)
    - Oklahoma (Oklahoma City, Tulsa), circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 13)
    - Tennessee (Norris), circa 1938 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 14)
    - Virginia (Lynchburg), circa 1935-circa 1942 (Box 25 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Art Week, circa 1940-circa 1941, (R 1178: 671-705) (Box 25 (hol), Folder 16)
    includes photo of Reginald Marsh, and photo of Louis Bouche, Reginald Marsh, and William Zorach; see also: Artist Files, Zorach, William (Box 24, F47)
  - Artists at Work, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R 1174: 132-263) (Box 25 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Artists at Work, 1936-1941, (R 1174: 132-263) (Box 25 (hol), Folder 18)
    includes photos of Edward Laning